# Minami Koma

FRONT-FND DEVELOPER

#### SUMMARY

Front-end developer with a background and passion for user experience and interaction design and strength in creative and strategic thinking. Learning and growing as a developer is important to me and I am currently working on multiple front-end projects. I am excellent at working in teams and enjoy collaboration with peers. I am also confident in the development of the frontend for e-commerce sites and will do my best to deliver modern interfaces.

#### CONTACT

- minamikoma24@gmail.com
- http://www.minamikoma. me/mysite/
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/minami-koma/
- https://github.com/minami-k/
- **\** 778-251-3672

#### **SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- SASS
- JavaScript
- React.is
- Node.js
- WordPress
- TypeScript
- Bootstrap
- MongoDB
- Firebase
- GitHub

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## PIPELINE, Inc.

## Front-end developer

July 2020 - April 2022 Kobe, Japan

- Created responsive websites for companies in different industries
- Maintained and updated WordPress websites
- Created banners and flyers with Adobe XD
- Customized WordPress theme to meet clients' needs
- Transferred a conventional website to EC site which increased sales by 35%

#### Accessnet

### Front-end developer

October 2020 - April 2022 Osaka, Japan

- · Listened to clients' ideas and made ideal websites for them
- Worked remotely as a outsourced developer, which allowed me to gain communication skills with the company and clients
- Created websites with great UI/UX to help users find relevant contents easily

## **PROJECTS**

Coffee Log App https://github.com/minami-k/coffee-log-app
HTML, CSS, React.js, React-Router, React Hooks, Firebase, Material UI
A memo dedicated to coffee lovers! Keep all your coffee recipes in one place so you won't forget the perfect ratio.

**Link Shortner** https://github.com/minami-k/linkshorten
HTML, CSS, React.js, React Hooks, shrtcode API, Bulma
A web application which makes long URLs shorter.

**Uber Clone Site** https://github.com/minami-k/clonesite

HTML, SASS

A clone site of Uber

Blog App https://github.com/minami-k/blogWithNodeJS

HTML, CSS, React.js, Node.js, EJS, MongoDB

With this blog, not only the front-end but the back-end is also implemented with Node.js.

## **EDUCATION HISTORY**

Diploma in Web Application Development

May 2021 Vancouver, Canada

Course taken: React.js/ Node.js/ SASS/ JavaScript

Cornerstone International Community College of Canada

Bachelor in Foreign Language Studies

April 2015 - March 2019

Osaka, Japan

Kansai University